30 seconds to explain why you should use creatine in season.
Number one, creatine will help with recovery, it will help you be a little bit more explosive
and help you fire quicker inside the game.
That's actually two things.
Number three, there is some evidence that creatine, at the very least, will help recover
from concussions, and there's some evidence that it may even prevent concussions because
you would actually ignite your nervous system to absorb or be able to handle a collision.
So it increases force production, it helps with recovery, it helps recover from some
type of brain trauma, and it very likely, not 100% but very likely, could prevent concussions.
So if you're not taking creatine as a high school football player in season, you're making
a massive mistake.
Also, you're just going to stay stronger longer so that you can get 315 for five on bench
for 10 reps.